https://www.swimleeds.org.uk/privacy-policy

Thank you for visiting the City of Leeds Swimming Club web site and for viewing our Privacy Policy. Our policy is clear:
We collect no information about you, other than information automatically collected and stored (see below) when you visit our web site unless you choose to provide that information to us.
Information automatically collected and stored
When you browse through any web site, certain information about your visit may be automatically collected. This site uses Google Analytics which collects the following basic information about visitors:
Type of user agent (web browser) used, software manufacture and version number.
Type of operating system
Screen colors (color processing ability of the users screen)
Java support
Flash version
Screen resolution
Network location and IP address
Can include country, county, city.
Hostname
Bandwidth (internet connection speed)
Time of visit
Pages visited
Time spent on each page of the website
Referring site statistics
The website (URI) the user came through in order to arrive at this website
Search engine query used (example: typing in a phrase into a search engine like Google)
We use this anonymous information
solely for statistical purposes in order to help us make our site more useful and relevant to visitors. Unless it is specifically stated otherwise, no additional information will be collected about you.
We do not collect any personally identifiable information. eg. Names, Email Addresses, Postal Addresses.
Personally provided information
You do not have to give us personal information to visit our web site.
However, all communications addressed to City of Leeds Swimming Club may be stored for reference purposes.
Disclosure
City of Leeds Swimming Club does not disclose, give, sell or transfer any personal information about our visitors, unless required by law.
Thank you for reading our Privacy Policy.
